<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView CannotScrollUntilEnd</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="long_long_sentence">
        Android is a mobile operating system developed by Google.
        It is based on a modified version of the Linux kernel and other open source software,
        and is designed primarily for touchscreen mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets.
        In addition, Google has developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars,
        and Wear OS for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface.
        Variants of Android are also used on game consoles, digital cameras, PCs and other electronics.
        Initially developed by Android Inc., which Google bought in 2005, Android was unveiled in 2007, with the first commercial Android device launched in September 2008.
        The current stable version is Android 9 "Pie", released in August 2018.
        Google released the first beta of the next release, Android Q, on Pixel phones in March 2019.
        The core Android source code is known as Android Open Source Project (AOSP), which is primarily licensed under the Apache License.
        Android is also associated with a suite of proprietary software developed by Google, called Google Mobile Services (GMS),[10] that frequently comes pre-installed on devices.
        This includes core apps such as Gmail, the application store/digital distribution platform Google Play and associated Google Play Services development platform,
        and usually includes the Google Chrome web browser and Google Search app.
        These apps are licensed by manufacturers of Android devices certified under standards imposed by Google,
        but AOSP has been used as the basis of competing Android ecosystems such as Amazon.com\'s Fire OS,
        which use their own equivalents to Google Mobile Services.</string>
</resources>
